<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ACCESSA</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ACCESSA</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:33:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/</guid>
      <description>Stoycho Gigov Role: Founder, CEO, Partner Finance and Controlling&#xA;LinkedIn Profile: Visit LinkedIn&#xA;Stoycho is an experienced management consultant and finance executive with a strong focus on global finance and controlling. His exceptional leadership skills, highlighted by his talent for building high performing finance teams and his impressive implementation excellence, have led to a track record of remarkable achievements.&#xA;With extensive experience spanning 25 years, Stoycho has designed and implemented global profitability and cost transparency models, worldwide integrated profitability analysis, plant performance solutions, transfer pricing models and comprehensive ERP process integrations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Areas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/core/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/core/</guid>
      <description>Financial Management Strategic planning and risk management to optimize financial performance and enhance profitability. ACCESSA GmbH specializes in comprehensive financial management services designed to enhance operational efficiency.&#xA;Business Partnership&#xA;Acting as strategic advisors, we ensure that financial insights guide to business decisions at every level.&#xA;Financial and Process Control&#xA;Implementing rigorous financial control to enhance the integrity of your operational processes.&#xA;Financial Organizations&#xA;Structuring your financial operations to meet your business objectives efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Imprint ACCESSA GmbH&#xA;Talstrasse 24 8852 Altendorf, SZ&#xA;Switzerland&#xA;Email: info@accessa.ch&#xA;Phone: +41 76 687 8628</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Data Protection Statement of ACCESSA GmbH Version effective as of 01.09.2023&#xA;With this Data Protection Statement, we, the ACCESSA GmbH (hereinafter &amp;ldquo;ACCESSA GmbH&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;), describe how we collect and further process personal data. This Data Protection Statement is not necessarily a comprehensive description of our data processing. It is possible that other data protection statements or General Terms and Conditions, Conditions of Participation, or similar documents are applicable to specific circumstances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>To contact us, please fill out the form below.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
